<properties count="1244">
  <property id="6743" name="Historical Heart apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0052" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="6786" name="Jordan Delight apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0053" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="6794" name="Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#053" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3568,4.85375</gps>
      <address>Sloterkade</address>
      <zipcode>1058 HD</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>Vondelpark - Museum Quarter</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>4</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>3</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2012-07-25</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>2</floor>
    <stairs>1</stairs>
    <size>90</size>
    <bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>2</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>1</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>water</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>1</fans>
    <balcony>1</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>normal</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>dvd</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>1</dishwasher>
    <oven>1</oven>
    <microwave>1</microwave>
    <grill>1</grill>
    <hob>1</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>1</freezer>
    <washingmachine>1</washingmachine>
    <dryer>1</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>1</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>1</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>1</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>0</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>150</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>15:00</check_in>
    <check_out>10:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Contemporary one bedroom apartment, for up to four people, in the Vondelpark area in Amsterdam, close to the Museum District. ]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Contemporary one bedroom apartment, for up to four people, in the Vondelpark area in Amsterdam, close to the Museum District. </strong></p>
<p>This stunning apartment is situated in a traditional Amsterdam building, recently renovated to effortlessly blend the modern with the historical. The living room is extremely spacious with antique ceilings and large windows that allow in plenty of natural light. The space is furnished with two sofas, a double sofa-bed, a dining table with seating for all guests and a television and&nbsp;DVD player. The open kitchen is modern and stylish and fully equipped with everything needed to prepare meals in the apartment, including an oven, hob, a microwave, a grill, a fridge, a freezer, a dishwasher, a toaster and a coffee machine. A flight of stairs leads to the second floor where you will find the traditional bedroom complete with sloping roof and original construction beams. The bedroom is spacious and comes furnished with&nbsp;a double bed,&nbsp;two single beds which can easily be put together and seating. Please note that there also is a baby cot available upon request. The bathroom with nice stained glass windows is contemporary and comes with a shower or a bath and another separate shower, washbasin and toilet. The top floor room also provides access to a charming balcony and is the ideal place to enjoy that morning coffee or evening glass of wine. Located close to the Vondelpark and the Museum Quarter, this apartment is ideal for business and leisure travellers after stylish accommodation in the heart of the city.Please be inform apartment has steep stairs.</p>
<p>Registration number: 0363 029E F19E 22A5 8AEA</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>This apartment is located on the outskirts of the Central Canal Belt just a 100 metres from Vondelpark and a short distance from Leidseplein and the Museum District. The view from the apartment is that of a wide Canal. Just a short distance from the apartment is the Museum Quarter home to several of the city’s largest museums including the Van Gogh Museum, Rijks Museum and the Stedelijk Museum. The district is also home to the Concert Hall and numerous bars, cafes and restaurants. Vondel Park, the largest park in the city, is just a 100 metre walk away and is the perfect place to relax on a warm afternoon. Leidseplein is close by and is one of Amsterdam’s nightlife hubs filled with bars, cafes, restaurants, nightclubs and live music venues. If you are a beer lover, why not visit the former Heineken Brewery, just a short distance from the apartment and although it no longer brews beer, you can take the tour and learn the history of the brewery and beer itself. This apartment is located in the perfect position, with numerous attractions within walking distance, and public transport links available for those places not reachable on foot.</p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,</p>
<p>Welcome to the ‘Canal Holiday’ apartment!</p>
<p>The owners of the apartment (bottom) will welcome you (most likely) at the apartment and help you with checking in and help you with other questions you might have upon arrival.</p>
<p><strong>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.</strong></p>
<p>Please inform us via borninfotos@gmail.com with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible (please note the number 1 at the end of the apartment name!).</p>
<p>Once you have arrived at <strong>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or have entered Amsterdam’s city ring</strong> please contact us on the check-in telephone number <strong>+31 655340345 </strong>(first contact number) or +31 652657283. This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check in</strong></p>
<p>Check-in is at the apartment (address: Sloterkade 19, 2nd floor, 1058 HD Amsterdam) between 14:00 and 20:00 local time (CET).
An early or late check-in can allways be requested and if possible, it cost 10 euro per full hour extra.</p>
<p><strong>Check out</strong></p>
<p>Check-out is between 8.00 and 11.00 local time (CET).
An early or late check-in can allways be requested and if possible, it cost 10 euro per full hour extra.</p>
<p><strong>Payment</strong></p>
<p>The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. This final payment is done by cash only. (Unless you have already paid by bank transfer). If you don't like to pay in cash, get in touch with us directly, details see bottom.</p>
<p><strong>Security Deposit</strong></p>
<p>We require a security deposit upon check in. We will hold <strong>Euro 150</strong> in cash upon check-in.
This amount will be returned to you in cash during check-out on the conditions that you have left the apartment in a good condition and no disturbance has occurred.</p>
<p>You pay no extra cleaning costs if you leave the apartment as you have found the accommodation.</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received and the security deposit is settled.</p>
<p>A washing machine and iron and ironing board are available in the apartment.</p>
<p>We look forward to meeting you upon your arrival and wish you a safe trip!</p>
<p>Kind regards,</p>
<p>Paul & Els</p>
<p>Paul Born (first contact person), phone: +31 655340345</p>
<p>or Els Born Oudeman, phone: +31 652657283</p>
<p>email: borninfotos@gmail.com</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="01_01.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_01_01.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 18:40:07"><![CDATA[Living Area Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="02.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_02.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Living Area other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="03_03.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_03_03.jpg" modified="2023-01-27 05:45:06"><![CDATA[Living area other angle 1 Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="04.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_04.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Living area with the view of stair Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="05.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_05.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Decorative details Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="06.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_06.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Sofa Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="07-1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_07-1.jpg" modified="2023-01-26 21:32:25"><![CDATA[Dining tabke with the view of kitchen Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="08_04.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_08_04.jpg" modified="2023-01-26 11:29:16"><![CDATA[Dining table Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="10-1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_10-1.jpg" modified="2023-01-31 07:57:24"><![CDATA[Dining table other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="11-.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_11-.jpg" modified="2022-05-01 13:03:45"><![CDATA[Dining table with the view of kitchen other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="12-06.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_12-06.jpg" modified="2022-05-01 13:03:49"><![CDATA[Kitchen Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="13-1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_13-1.jpg" modified="2023-01-28 18:33:14"><![CDATA[Kitchen other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="14.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_14.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Bedroom Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="15_10.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_15_10.jpg" modified="2022-05-01 13:05:22"><![CDATA[Bedroom with the view of balcony Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="16_07.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_16_07.jpg" modified="2022-05-01 13:05:23"><![CDATA[Bedroom with single beds Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="17.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_17.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Bedroom Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="18_02.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_18_02.jpg" modified="2023-03-20 10:57:25"><![CDATA[Double bed Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="19.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_19.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Double bed other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="20_08.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_20_08.jpg" modified="2022-09-20 14:58:32"><![CDATA[Bathroom Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="21_09.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_21_09.jpg" modified="2023-01-27 18:16:09"><![CDATA[Bathroom other angle Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="22.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_22.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Landmark Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="23.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_23.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Neighborhood Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="24.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_24.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Neighborhood Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="25.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/6794_25.jpg" modified="2022-04-29 09:08:35"><![CDATA[Canal View Canal Holiday apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2012-07-25 10:31:19</created>
    <modified>2024-05-28 12:25:32</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="6861" name="Plantage Park suite Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0318" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8239" name="365-Inn apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0054" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8318" name="Love Life Loft apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0009" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8325" name="Central Blue Boat" identifier="1472" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8326" name="Frans Hals Deluxe" identifier="2066" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8327" name="Grand Nieuwmarkt" identifier="1475" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8328" name="Herman Brood Deluxe" identifier="2069" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8329" name="Jeroen Bosch Deluxe" identifier="2070" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8330" name="Johannes Vermeer Deluxe" identifier="2061" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8331" name="Jordaan Nine Streets" identifier="1477" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8332" name="Karel Appel Deluxe" identifier="2062" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8333" name="Nieuwegrachtje A" identifier="1470" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8334" name="Nieuwegrachtje B" identifier="1471" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8335" name="Piet Mondriaan Deluxe" identifier="2063" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8336" name="Rembrandt van Rijn Deluxe" identifier="2064" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8337" name="Vincent van Gogh Deluxe" identifier="2065" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8338" name="Westerndock" identifier="1474" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8339" name="Westerndock Executive Apartment" identifier="1473" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8340" name="Willem de Kooning Deluxe" identifier="2068" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8341" name="Zuidas Executive" identifier="1476" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8487" name="Old Warehouse apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0057" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="8810" name="Keizersgracht Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0058" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9049" name="Voetboog apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0315" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9054" name="Valerius apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0259" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9275" name="Gravelandse apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0322" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9340" name="Nieuwmarkt-Waag Apartment 1" identifier="1581" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9341" name="Nieuwmarkt-Waag Apartment 2" identifier="1703" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9508" name="Jordaan Flower Canal Deluxe" identifier="1465" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9629" name="Da Costa III apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0218" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9683" name="Montelbaan houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="#035" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9684" name="Hendrick de Keyser apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0060" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9685" name="Multatuli Luxury apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0061" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9686" name="Herengracht Canal studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0062" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9687" name="Jordaan Orange house Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0063" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9688" name="Brewers Loft apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0064" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9694" name="Prins Hendrik II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0098" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9695" name="Amstel Duplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0069" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9696" name="Hemony Duplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0070" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9697" name="Waterloo apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0071" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9698" name="Garden House" identifier="BBA0279" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9764" name="Rustic Charm apartment Amstelveen" identifier="BBA0159" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="9824" name="Mart studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0185" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10394" name="Da Costa I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0219" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10585" name="Looiersgracht I apartment" identifier="BBA0280" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10596" name="Looiersgracht II apartment" identifier="BBA0281" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10656" name="Cool I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0176" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10751" name="KNSM apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0080" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10869" name="Saturnus houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0072" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10935" name="Olympic Stadium I studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0082" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10936" name="Olympic Stadium II studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0083" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="10954" name="Haarlemmer I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0388" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11113" name="Canal Side apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0084" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11159" name="The Grand Canal House" identifier="1466" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11271" name="Visseringstaete canalview Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0085" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11274" name="Visseringstaete skyline Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0086" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11277" name="Visseringstaete penthouse Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0087" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11355" name="Frederik Triplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0088" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11485" name="Air apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0127" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11488" name="Water apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0128" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11490" name="Fire apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0129" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11491" name="ACCA Canal II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#062" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11493" name="Amsterdam City Canal 3 Apartment" identifier="BBA0282" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11495" name="Earth apartment Amsterdam" identifier="819" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11508" name="Korte Leidse studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0079" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11509" name="Weteringschans Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0117" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11572" name="Quartier Latin apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0138" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11589" name="Wilhelm Vondel apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0109" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11619" name="Garden studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0124" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11620" name="Bel Etage studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0125" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11621" name="Superior apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0126" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11622" name="Prince Canal I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0119" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11623" name="Prince Canal II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0120" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11688" name="Pata Negra apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0130" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11698" name="A-Location apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0310" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11715" name="Old Masters apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0389" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11722" name="Nieuwmarkt houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0390" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11793" name="Jan Steen A apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0303" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11799" name="Dam apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0319" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11804" name="Wendy's houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0407" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11805" name="Jordaan City studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0336" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11807" name="Olympic Stadium apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0391" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11884" name="Archery I Deluxe" identifier="1480" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11885" name="Archery II" identifier="1478" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11886" name="Archery III" identifier="1479" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11892" name="Studio Jordaan" identifier="BBA0283" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11893" name="Triplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0131" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11894" name="Dormir Jordaan apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0132" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11896" name="Prinsengracht 969 studio Amsterdam" identifier="#081" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="11897" name="Jacob Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0216" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12018" name="Novel apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0168" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12030" name="Amstel apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0157" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12032" name="Luxury Canal suite Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0158" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12035" name="Canal Vitality apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0392" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12078" name="Nassau City apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0316" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12162" name="Carre Deluxe I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0133" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12163" name="Carre Deluxe II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0139" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12164" name="Carre Deluxe III apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0140" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12165" name="Carre Deluxe IV apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0141" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12166" name="Carre Deluxe V apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0152" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12167" name="Carre Deluxe VI apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0153" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12197" name="Cornelis apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0301" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12233" name="Stadhouderskade apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0393" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12290" name="Amstel Deluxe apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0137" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12294" name="Rapenburgerstraat 8" identifier="BBA0284" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12391" name="Carre Family I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0148" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12395" name="Carre Family II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0149" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12648" name="Dam A apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0142" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12650" name="Dam B apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0143" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12651" name="Dam C apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0144" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12652" name="Dam D apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0145" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12653" name="Dam E apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0146" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12654" name="Dam F apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0147" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12756" name="Leidse Square 1 apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0154" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="12757" name="Leidse Square 2 apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0155" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13403" name="Vijzels studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0221" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13435" name="Christof I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0313" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13475" name="Mid-Century apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0337" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13570" name="4 You To Enjoy apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0235" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13624" name="Vondelpark House Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0106" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13645" name="RAI apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0150" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13686" name="Amstel I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0317" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13827" name="Anjeliers apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0320" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13851" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 12" identifier="1445" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13852" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 13" identifier="1446" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13853" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 2" identifier="1435" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13854" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 4" identifier="1437" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13855" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 5" identifier="1438" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13856" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 8" identifier="1441" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13857" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 9" identifier="1442" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13899" name="Tommy's apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#150" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13900" name="Cool II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0177" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13901" name="Cool III apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0170" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13902" name="Cool IV apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0171" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13903" name="Cool V apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0172" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13904" name="Cool VI apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0173" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13905" name="Cool VII apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0174" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="13906" name="Cool VIII apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0175" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14099" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 1" identifier="1434" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14100" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 11" identifier="1444" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14101" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 15" identifier="1448" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14102" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 3" identifier="1436" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14103" name="Sarphatipark Apartment 7" identifier="1440" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14430" name="New Markt apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0156" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14656" name="Bergstraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0394" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14703" name="Jordaan Duplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0160" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14704" name="Jordaan Triplex apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0161" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14705" name="Elandsgracht apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0178" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14706" name="Jan Steen apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0162" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14707" name="Helmerstraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0206" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="14708" name="Funenpark apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0207" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15059" name="Prince Charles apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0163" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15060" name="Prince Harry apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0164" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15061" name="Prince William apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0165" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15062" name="Princess Diana apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0166" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15063" name="Jordaan Deluxe apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0167" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15175" name="BB Canalicious apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0285" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15870" name="Sluice apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0182" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15871" name="Family house Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0246" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15872" name="The Weavery I studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0286" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15873" name="The Weavery II studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0287" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15874" name="Eerste Nassaustraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0247" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15875" name="Kade19 apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0267" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15901" name="Prinsengracht canal house Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0180" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="15902" name="Prinsengracht studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0181" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="16774" name="Plantage apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0288" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="16776" name="House of Sophie apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0243" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="17678" name="Kerkstraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0190" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18079" name="Kwakerstraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0214" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18177" name="Trendy Beach apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0244" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18178" name="Trendy Beach studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0245" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18179" name="Robbchie's Garden house Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0251" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18181" name="Jordam apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0241" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18327" name="Korte Prins I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0261" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18328" name="Lijnbaans I apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0262" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18329" name="Lindengracht apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0254" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18330" name="Prins II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0255" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18331" name="Prins III apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0256" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18332" name="Korte Prins II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0271" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18333" name="Lijnbaans II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0272" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18334" name="City Centre apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0269" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18335" name="Amstel Fab apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0294" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18336" name="Captainsplace houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0296" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18490" name="Grand Orange house Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0199" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18491" name="Grand Brewers apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0200" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18695" name="Bellamystraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0257" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18847" name="86 Sous Apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0225" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="18848" name="B28 Houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0234" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="19269" name="Argonaut apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0258" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="19603" name="Haarlemmer III apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0298" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20172" name="Jordaan Laurier Apartment A" identifier="1481" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20173" name="Jordaan Laurier Apartment B" identifier="1482" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20174" name="Jordaan Laurier Apartment C" identifier="1483" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20175" name="Jordaan Laurier Apartment D" identifier="1484" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20176" name="Jordaan Laurier Apartment E" identifier="1485" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="20248" name="Prinsen apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#100" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3669,4.88278</gps>
      <address>Prinsengracht</address>
      <zipcode>1016</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>De 9 Straatjes</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>2</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>3</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2013-03-26</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-10-01</available_end>
    <floor>2</floor>
    <stairs>2</stairs>
    <size>90</size>
    <bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>0</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>water</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>1</fans>
    <balcony>1</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>normal</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>dvd</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>1</dishwasher>
    <oven>0</oven>
    <microwave>1</microwave>
    <grill>0</grill>
    <hob>1</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>1</freezer>
    <washingmachine>0</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>1</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>1</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>40</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>200</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Amazingly charming, one bedroom apartment, for up to two people in the trendy Nine Streets in the Jordaan area of Amsterdam.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Amazingly charming, one bedroom apartment for up to two people, in the trendy Nine Streets.</strong></p>
<p>If you are looking for something just that little bit different, then this 90m2 apartment, situated in a historic building on one of the main Amsterdam canals, could be what you are looking for. The warm and welcoming living area, contains two sofas, a TV and DVD player, a well stocked bookcase, a coffee table and interesting art pieces. The kitchen is finished to a high standard and includes a microwave, hob, fridge freezer and a dishwasher. There is also a glass dining table with chairs. The beautiful ensuite bedroom, up a winding staircase, is nestled beneath the beams, offers views across the rooftops and is furnished with a double bed. The well-finished bathroom is fitted with a bath, shower and toilet. Amenities include Wifi, a hair dryer, fans and a front facing balcony – great to sit and enjoy a glass of wine or a cold beer. In short, a beautiful, unique and surprising apartment, right in the heart of the city. Please note that there are steep stairs to climb in the apartment.</p>
<p>Registration Number: 0363 85F1 CF0E 660E FFF6</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>The Prinsengracht is one of Amsterdam’s four main canals. In the heart of the trendy Jordaan district, with its eclectic collection of boutiques, cafés and restaurants, the apartment is a perfect base from which to explore the city (and its nightlife).  </p>
<p>The Palace on Dam Square, the hectic Kalverstraat shopping street and the calm of the Vondel park are all only a short walk away. Visit the tempting Lindengracht food market on a Saturday morning, or walk round the corner to the farmers' market on the Noordermarkt. Also within easy walking distance are the “Negen straatjes” (9 streets), home to many of Amsterdam’s exciting smaller boutiques. Just a five minute walk away is the Museumplein, home to the Van Gogh Museum, the newly reopened Stedelijk Museum of Modern Art and the Rijksmuseum with its collection of world renowned masterworks.  Something for every taste!</p>
<p>For those of you who want to venture a little further afield, hop on one of the many trams to take you across Amsterdam. The main train station, Central Station is also just a stone’s throw away.</p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,</p>
<p>Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!</p>
<p><b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.</b></p>
<p>Please inform us via ericbnb@yahoo.com with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible. </p>
<p>Once you have arrived at <strong>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring</strong>  please contact us on our check-in telephone <strong>+31625137414</strong>. This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><b>Check-in</b></p>
<p>Check-in is at the apartment (address: Prinsengracht 667) from 14:00.An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival.</p>
<p><b>Check-out</b></p>
<p>Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Payment</strong></p>
<p>The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.</p>
<p><strong>Security Deposit</strong></p>
<p>We require a security deposit upon check in. We will hold <strong>Euro 200</strong> in cash upon check-in.This amount will be returned to you in cash during check-out on the conditions that you have left the apartment in a good condition and no disturbance has occurred. Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received and the security deposit is settled.</p>
<p>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</p>
<p>We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!</p>
<p>Kind regards,</p>
<p>Eric Malferrari</p>
<p>+31 625137414</p>
<p>ericbnb@yahoo.com</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="living area.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_living%20area.jpg" modified="2021-10-11 12:46:41"><![CDATA[Living Area with the view of Balcony Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="living area1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_living%20area1.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:45"><![CDATA[Living area other angle Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="living area2.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_living%20area2.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:46"><![CDATA[Living Area with the view of Balcony other angle 1 Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="decorative photo 1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_decorative%20photo%201.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:46"><![CDATA[Decorative details in living area Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="living area3.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_living%20area3.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Living Area with the of stairs Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="dining table.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_dining%20table.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Dining table Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="decorative photo.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_decorative%20photo.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Decorative details Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="dining table 1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_dining%20table%201.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Dining Table with the of Balcony Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="kitchen.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_kitchen.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:46"><![CDATA[Kitchen Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="bedroom.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_bedroom.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Bedroom Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="bedroom1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_bedroom1.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:49"><![CDATA[Bedroom other angle Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="decorative photo 2.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_decorative%20photo%202.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:48"><![CDATA[Bedroom other angle 1 Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="bathroom.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_bathroom.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Bathroom Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="decorative photo in bathroom.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_decorative%20photo%20in%20bathroom.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Decorative details photo Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="outdoor 1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_outdoor%201.jpg" modified="2022-01-29 16:21:47"><![CDATA[Outdoor Photo Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="18.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_18.jpg" modified="2014-03-05 19:44:03"><![CDATA[Outdoor Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="20.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/20248_20.jpg" modified="2014-01-15 12:42:20"><![CDATA[Canal View Prinsen apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2013-03-25 15:55:40</created>
    <modified>2024-08-23 14:46:27</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="21570" name="West City apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#419" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3795,4.84816</gps>
      <address>Baetostraat</address>
      <zipcode>1055 ER </zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>Baarsjes - Bos en Lommer</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>4</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>2</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2021-07-01</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>1</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>40</size>
    <bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>1</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>0</fans>
    <balcony>1</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>1</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>flatscreen</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>0</oven>
    <microwave>1</microwave>
    <grill>1</grill>
    <hob>0</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>1</freezer>
    <washingmachine>0</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>50</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>0</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Comfortable one-bedroom apartment with garden, for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Comfortable one-bedroom apartment with garden, for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.</strong></p>
<p>This stylish and comfortable apartment, is perfect for two couples or a family, wanting to explore the city but also wanting some time to relax. With easy access to the city centre and far enough away from it all, this apartment has the best of both worlds. The cosy living area has a large sofa
(converts to a double bed), where you will be able to sit and watch the flat screen
television (with cable). There is a dining table too, with ample room for four. There is a microwave, a kettle, and a coffee machine. The bedroom is simply decorated, with a
double bed and extra washbasin. The bathroom has a shower. The garden, accessible from the kitchenette down a staircase, is a wonderful spot to relax after a busy day of sightseeing.
With enough garden furniture, you will be able to sit down and enjoy a glass of
wine in the evening sunshine.&nbsp; If you are looking for an apartment with the bonus of some outside space, then this could be what you are looking for. With both balcony AND garden, you will be able to enjoy the Amsterdam sunshine to your heart’s content.</p>
<p>Registration number: 0363 A10B D120 6049 82F5</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>This apartment is
situated in the West of the City, and is close to all the amenities you may
need. Want a bite to eat? Restaurants and cafés are plentiful, and for those
who prefer to cook at home – there are plenty of shops in the neighbourhood
too. If relaxation is your thing, then the
Erasmus Park is a stone’s throw away, or take a walk to the famous Vondel Park.
If you like  shopping, a short tram ride will take you to the heart of
Amsterdam’s most exclusive shopping street, the PC Hooftstraat, with designer
shops galore. </p>
<p>The Palace on Dam
Square and the hectic Kalverstraat shopping street are all only a cycle or tram
ride away. Visit the tempting Lindengracht food market on a Saturday morning,
or the farmers' market on the Noordermarkt. Just half an hour away is the
Museumplein, home to the Van Gogh Museum, the newly reopened Stedelijk Museum
of Modern Art and the Rijksmuseum with its collection of world renowned
masterworks. Something for every taste!</p>
<p>The apartment is well
situated for getting around Amsterdam. Central Station is just a short tram
ride away. </p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,<br />
<br />
Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!<br />
<br />
<b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.<br />
<br />
</b>Please inform us via email info@10minutes2center.nl<em> </em>with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible.<br />
<br />
Once you have arrived at <b>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring </b> please contact us on our check-in telephone +31 630040156</p>
<p>This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check-in</strong></p>
<p>
Check-in is at the apartment (address:<em> </em>Baetostraat 9HS<em></em>) from 14:00.</p>
<p>
An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be
requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival.</p>
<p><strong>Check-out</strong></p>
<p>
Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>From Schiphol</strong><br />
<strong>Taxi</strong>: from the airport to <strong>10minutes2center</strong> is 15 km. A taxi from the airport to <strong>10minutes2center</strong> costs about <strong>40 </strong>Euro,-. </p>
<p>Apartment 1, theme the Netherlands: Baetostraat 9h<strong>Train from Schiphol airport</strong>: journey takes about 30 minutes and costs
about 6 Euro,-. Take the train from Schiphol airport to Station Sloterdijk. There you take bus 15 and get off at the Bos en Lommerplein. Walk back a bit towards the Bos en Lommerplein and turn right at the traffic light. Proceed until supermarket Dirk van den Broek en turn left to cross the street. On the opposite side of the street turn right. After about 50 meters a Turkish eatery "Birtat" can be found on the corner of the Baetostraat. <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme the Netherlands is located at Baetostraat 9h. </p>
<p><b>Public transport from Amsterdam Central Station</b>: Bus 21: direction Geuzenveld . Get off at stop Egidiusstraat. Walk from the tram-/ bus stop in the direction the bus is going. After about 150 meters a Turkish eatery "Birtat" can be found on the right, on the corner of the Baetostraat. <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme the Netherlands is located at Baetostraat 9h. </p>
<p><b>By car from direction Den Haag/Utrecht/Amersfoort</b>: From the A10 take exit S105 At the exit, go straight passing two traffic lights (these are close to each other) to get on the S104 and keep right. At the end of the exit turn right at the traffic lights. You go straight ahead and where you see Domino's Pizza on the right, you turn left into the Egidiusstraat. Turn left at the end of the street to the Leeuwendalersweg. The sixth street on the left is the Baetostraat. <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme the Netherlands is located at Baetostraat 9h. </p>
<p>By car from direction Zaandam: take exit S104. At the end of the exit turn left. Go straight ahead at the 2 traffic lights and where you see Domino's Pizza on the right, you turn left into the Egidiusstraat. Turn left at the end of the street into the Leeuwendalersweg and the sixth street on the left is the Baetostraat. <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme the Netherlands is located at Baetostraat 9h. </p>
<p>Click <a href="file://localhost/javascript/kaart()">here</a> for a map. </p>
<p><strong>Parking</strong> We recommend parking your car in the guarded and covered parking "P + R" under the Bos en Lommerplein at Leeuwendalersweg 23b. Parking in a "P + R" costs 8 Euro per 24 hours including a return ticket for public transport for up to 5 people, depending on the number of people. Follow the above directions until right after the 2 traffic lights. Turn left at KFC. Follow this road en the curve to the left. At the end of the road you will see the entrance of the parking. Look at www.parkerenamsterdam.nl for more information. Fast, flexible and free with the bike through Amsterdam? Borrow
one or two well-maintained bikes from <strong>10minutes2center</strong>! </p>
<p><strong>Payment</strong></p>
<p>
The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received</p>
<p>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</p>
<p>We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!<br />
<br />
Kind regards,</p>
<p>Janeth</p>
<p>+31 630040156</p>
<p> </p>
<p>info@10minutes2center.nl</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="01.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_01.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:13"><![CDATA[Overall View West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="02.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_02.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:14"><![CDATA[Living Room with Dining Area West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="03.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_03.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:15"><![CDATA[Dining Area Overview with Plasma TV West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="04.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_04.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:16"><![CDATA[Dining Area with Living Room View West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="05.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_05.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:17"><![CDATA[Living Room Sofa West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="06.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_06.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:22:18"><![CDATA[Living Room Other Angle West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="imgv1.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_imgv1.jpg" modified="2024-08-20 15:52:42"><![CDATA[Kitchenette West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="imgv2.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_imgv2.jpg" modified="2024-08-22 18:57:00"><![CDATA[Kitchenette other angle West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="07.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_07.jpg" modified="2019-10-01 06:28:56"><![CDATA[Balcony with Garden ViewWest City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="13.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_13.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 11:41:33"><![CDATA[Bedroom West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="14.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_14.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 11:41:33"><![CDATA[Bedroom Double Bed West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="15.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_15.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 11:41:33"><![CDATA[Bedroom with Sink West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="16.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_16.jpg" modified="2014-05-27 00:01:27"><![CDATA[Bedroom Other Angle West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="21570-gl-01.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_21570-gl-01.jpg" modified="2016-01-27 14:04:57"><![CDATA[Bathroom West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0001.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_0001.jpg" modified="2019-11-15 09:03:05"><![CDATA[Shower West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0002.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_0002.jpg" modified="2016-03-16 15:47:06"><![CDATA[Toilet West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5845.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_5845.jpg" modified="2017-09-14 17:14:19"><![CDATA[Garden Other angle 1 West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5846.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_5846.jpg" modified="2018-04-17 09:11:47"><![CDATA[Garden Other angle 2 West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_6741.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_6741.jpg" modified="2023-01-29 10:19:37"><![CDATA[Garden Overview West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5849.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_5849.jpg" modified="2018-04-17 09:18:49"><![CDATA[Garden other angle 4 West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5850.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_5850.jpg" modified="2018-05-28 05:44:41"><![CDATA[Outside View of apartment West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_6743.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_img_6743.jpg" modified="2023-01-26 16:56:50"><![CDATA[Garden View West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="21.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_21.jpg" modified="2017-07-19 05:21:26"><![CDATA[Lake View West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="22.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_22.jpg" modified="2017-07-19 05:21:26"><![CDATA[Outdoor View West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="23.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21570_23.jpg" modified="2017-07-19 05:21:26"><![CDATA[Outdoor with Lake Overview West City apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2013-11-19 10:19:35</created>
    <modified>2024-07-12 10:29:41</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="21582" name="Maritime Museum Residence 1" identifier="1528" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21583" name="Maritime Museum Residence 2" identifier="1529" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21584" name="Maritime Museum Residence 3" identifier="1530" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21585" name="Maritime Museum Penthouse" identifier="1531" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21587" name="Jordaan Marnix Apartment C" identifier="1467" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21595" name="Queen apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0367" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21597" name="Jordaan Noordermarkt Apartment A" identifier="1494" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21609" name="Ambiente apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0368" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21610" name="Pipe City apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0369" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21611" name="Thailand apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#419" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="114" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam Hotels"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3769,4.85069</gps>
      <address>Marieken van Nimwegenstraat</address>
      <zipcode>1055 BK</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>Baarsjes - Bos en Lommer</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>4</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>2</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2021-07-01</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>0</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>45</size>
    <bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>1</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>0</fans>
    <balcony>0</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>flatscreen</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>1</oven>
    <microwave>1</microwave>
    <grill>1</grill>
    <hob>1</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>0</freezer>
    <washingmachine>0</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>50</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>0</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Compact and comfortable one-bedroom apartment for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Compact and comfortable one-bedroom apartment for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.</strong></p>
<p>This comfortable accommodation, with an Asian touch, wooden floors and large windows that allow in plenty of natural light, is perfect for two couples or a family.<strong> </strong>The bright and
cheerful living area has a large sofa (converts into a double bed),&nbsp; a flat
screen television with cable and a dining table for four. The separate kitchen
is well equipped, and includes an oven, microwave, fridge and freezer. The bedroom has a comfortable
double bed. The bathroom is modern and features a toilet, washbasin and shower. This apartment has everything
you need for a stay in Amsterdam. Located close to the Erasmus park and easy reachable by public transport, makes this a perfect base from which to explore the city. Breakfast can be requested when booking (€ 15,- per person per day). The host will provide a refrigerator stocked with bread, milk, cheese, eggs, meats and juice. </p>
<p>We offer parking rental for Euro 20 per day</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>This apartment is
situated in the West of the City, and is close to all the amenities you may
need. Want a bite to eat? Restaurants and cafés are plentiful, and for those
who prefer cooking at home – there are plenty of shops in the neighbourhood
too.  If relaxation is your thing, then the
Erasmus Park is a stone’s throw away, or take a walk to the famous Vondel Park.
If you like  shopping, a short bus ride will take you to the heart of
Amsterdam’s most exclusive shopping street, the PC Hooftstraat, with designer
shops galore. </p>
<p>The Palace on Dam
Square and the hectic Kalverstraat shopping street are all only a cycle or bus ride away. Visit the tempting Lindengracht food market on a Saturday morning,
or the farmers' market on the Noordermarkt. Just half an hour away is the
Museumplein, home to the Van Gogh Museum, the newly reopened Stedelijk Museum
of Modern Art and the Rijksmuseum with its collection of world renowned
masterworks.  Something for every taste!</p>
<p>The apartment is well
situated for getting around Amsterdam. Central Station is just a short bus ride away. </p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,<br />
<br />
Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!<br />
<br />
<b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.<br />
<br />
</b>Please inform us via email info@10minutes2center.nl with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Once you have arrived at <strong>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring</strong> please call +31 630040156.This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check-in</strong></p>
<p>Check-in is at the apartment (address: Marieken van Nimwegenstraat 11A <em></em>) from 14:00.<br />
<br />
An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be
requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival. <u><br />
</u><br />
<strong>Check-out</strong> </p>
<p>Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment. </p>
<p><strong>Payment</strong></p>
<p>The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received.
</p>
<p><strong>Directions</strong></p>
<p><strong>Trein</strong>: om in Bos en Lommer te komen kunt u de trein vanaf Schiphol nemen. De reistijd is ongeveer 30 minuten en de kosten zijn ongeveer Euro<strong> </strong>6. U neemt de trein van Schiphol naar station Sloterdijk. Daar neemt u bus 15 en stapt uit bij het Bos en Lommerplein. U loopt in de richting waarin ook de bus gaat. Bij de
oversteekplaats linksaf en aan de overkant doorlopen tot het eind. De eerste rechtsaf de Marieken van Nimwegenstraat in. Na ongeveer 150 meter op nummer 11a (hoek Marieken van Nimwegenstraat/Lanseloetstraat), aan de rechterkant van de straat vindt u 10minutes2center thema Thailand. </p>
<p><strong>Met openbaar vervoer vanaf Centraal Station Amsterdam</strong>: Bus 21: richting Geuzenveld. Uitstappen op halte "Egidiusstraat". U loopt vanaf de tram- en bushalte een stukje terug naar “Domino’s Pizza”. Hier de Egidiusstraat inlopen. Tweede straat rechtsaf de Marieken van Nimwegenstraat in. Na ongeveer 150 meter op nummer 11a (hoek Marieken van Nimwegenstraat/Lanseloetstraat), aan de linkerkant van de straat vindt u 10minutes2center thema Thailand.</p>
<p><strong>Met de auto vanuit richting Den Haag/Utrecht/Amersfoort</strong>: Vanaf de A10, neemt u de afslag S105, Onderaan de afslag gaat u rechtdoor bij beide stoplichten (deze staan vlak na elkaar) en houdt vervolgens
rechts aan, zo komt u op afrit s104. Aan het eind van de afslag gaat u bij de stoplichten rechtsaf. U gaat rechtdoor bij de volgende 2 stoplichten en waar u Domino's Pizza ziet gaat u rechtsaf de Egidiusstraat in. Tweede straat rechts de Marieken van Nimwegenstraat in. Na ongeveer 150 meter op nummer 11a (hoek Marieken van Nimwegenstraat/Lanseloetstraat), aan de linkerkant van de straat
vindt u 10minutes2center thema Thailand.</p>
<p>Met de auto vanuit de richting Zaandam neemt u afslag s104. Onderaan de afslag gaat u linksaf. U gaat rechtdoor bij de volgende 2 stoplichten en waar u Domino's Pizza ziet gaat u rechtsaf de Egidiusstraat in. Tweede straat rechts de Marieken van Nimwegenstraat in. Na ongeveer 150 meter op nummer 11a (hoek Marieken van Nimwegenstraat/Lanseloetstraat), aan de linkerkant van de straat vindt u 10minutes2center thema Thailand. </p>
<p>Klik hier voor de kaart.</p>
<p><strong>Parkeren</strong> Wij adviseren om uw auto te parkeren in de bewaakte en overdekte parkeerplaats "P+R" onder het Bos en Lommerplein
(Leeuwendalersweg 23b). Parkeren op een "P+R" kost Euro<strong> </strong>8.00 per 24 uur inclusief openbaar vervoer kaartjes voor maximaal 5 personen, afhankelijk van het aantal personen. Als u de routebeschrijving hierboven heeft gevolgd tot na de 2 stoplichten gaat u linksaf bij KFC. Deze weg volgen langs het Gulden Winckelplantsoen, de bocht naar links volgen. Na 150 meter vindt u links de ingang na de parkeergarage. Snel, flexibel en gratis met de fiets door Amsterdam? Leen 1 of 2 goed onderhouden fietsen van 10minutes2center! Kijk op www.parkerenamsterdam.nl voor meer informatie.</p>
<p><strong>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</strong><br />
<br />
We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!<br />
<br />
Kind regards,</p>
<p>Janeth</p>
<p>+31 630040156</p>
<p>info@10minutes2center.nl</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a pre-payment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The 50% pre-payment is non-refundable at any time, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 21 days before the start of the stay will be charged with 100% of the balance due.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a pre-payment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The 50% pre-payment is non-refundable at any time, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 21 days before the start of the stay will be charged with 100% of the balance due.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="img_6698.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_6698.jpg" modified="2020-08-10 12:15:57"><![CDATA[Living Area Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_6699.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_6699.jpg" modified="2020-08-10 12:15:57"><![CDATA[Living Area other angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="06.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_06.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Dining Area Other Angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="08.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_08.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Kitchen Overview Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="10.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_10.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Kitchen with Large Window Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="11.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_11.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Kitchen Other Angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="12.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_12.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Double Bed Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="13.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_13.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Double Bed Other Angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="14.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_14.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Bathroom Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="15.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_15.jpg" modified="2020-08-07 08:26:49"><![CDATA[Bathroom Other Angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_6700.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_6700.jpg" modified="2023-01-24 21:23:54"><![CDATA[Sofa Bed Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_6701.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_6701.jpg" modified="2021-07-05 11:52:29"><![CDATA[Sofa bed other angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_6702.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_6702.jpg" modified="2023-07-03 10:24:07"><![CDATA[Sofa bed other angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="16.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_16.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 14:19:46"><![CDATA[Main Door Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_5884.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_5884.jpg" modified="2017-07-30 21:55:12"><![CDATA[Main door other angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_5881.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_5881.jpg" modified="2017-08-19 14:10:41"><![CDATA[Play ground Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_5877.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_5877.jpg" modified="2018-04-17 09:14:16"><![CDATA[Water View Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5878.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_5878.jpg" modified="2018-04-17 09:14:18"><![CDATA[Park Thailand apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_5882.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21611_img_5882.jpg" modified="2018-05-12 21:56:08"><![CDATA[Water View other angle Thailand apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2013-11-27 13:10:24</created>
    <modified>2024-05-28 12:27:28</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="21612" name="Ibiza Dream apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0371" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21619" name="Canal Nassau apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0372" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21622" name="Brazil apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#419" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="114" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam Hotels"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3769,4.85069</gps>
      <address>Marieken van Nimwegenstraat</address>
      <zipcode>1055 BK</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>Baarsjes - Bos en Lommer</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>4</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>2</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2021-07-01</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>0</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>40</size>
    <bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>1</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>0</fans>
    <balcony>0</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>1</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>flatscreen</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>1</oven>
    <microwave>1</microwave>
    <grill>1</grill>
    <hob>1</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>1</freezer>
    <washingmachine>0</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>50</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>0</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Compact and comfortable one-bedroom apartment with garden, for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Compact and comfortable one-bedroom apartment with garden, for up to four guests, in the trendy and upcoming West area of Amsterdam.</strong></p>
<p>This comfortable accommodation, with an asian touch, woorden floors and large windows that allow plenty of natural light, is perfect for two couples or a family. The bright and cheerful living area has a large sofa (converts into a double bed), and a flatscreen television with cable. The separate kitchen is well equipped, and includes an oven, microwave, fridge and freezer. There is also a dining table for four. The bedroom has a comfortable double bed. The bathroom is modern and features a toilet, washbasin and shower. The bonus of the apartment is the garden, where you can enjoy a morning cup of coffee or evening glass of wine. This apartment has everything you need for a stay in Amsterdam, located close to the Erasmus park and easy reachable by public transport, makes this a perfect base from which to explore the city. Breakfast can be requested when booking (€ 15,- per person per day). The host will provide a refrigerator stocked with bread,milk, cheese, eggs, meats and juice.</p>
<p data-pm-slice="1 1 []">We offer parking rental for Euro 20 per day</p>
<p> </p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>This apartment is
situated in the West of the City, and is close to all the amenities you may
need. Want a bite to eat? Restaurants and cafés are plentiful, and for those
who prefer to cook at home – there are plenty of shops in the neighborhood
too.  If relaxation is your thing, then the
Erasmus Park is a stone’s throw away, or take a walk to the famous Vondel Park.
If you like shopping, a short bus ride will bring you to the heart of
Amsterdam’s most exclusive shopping street, the PC Hooftstraat, with designer
shops galore. </p>
<p>The Palace on Dam
Square and the hectic Kalverstraat shopping street are all only a cycle or bus ride away. Visit the tempting Lindengracht food market on a Saturday morning,
or the farmers' market on the Noordermarkt. Just half an hour away is the
Museumplein, home to the Van Gogh Museum, the newly reopened Stedelijk Museum
of Modern Art and the Rijksmuseum with its collection of world renowned
masterworks.  Something for every taste!</p>
<p>The apartment is well
situated for getting around Amsterdam. Central Station is just a short bus ride away. </p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,<br />
<br />
Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!<br />
<br />
<b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.<br />
<br />
</b>Please inform us via email info@10minutes2center.nl with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Once you have arrived at <b>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring</b> please call +31 63004015.This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check-in</strong></p>
<p>
Check-in is at the apartment (address: Marieken van Nimwegenstraat 11B) from 14:00.</p>
<p>
An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be
requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival.</p>
<p><strong>Check-out</strong></p>
<p>
Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment. </p>
<p><strong>Payment</strong></p>
<p>
The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received.
</p>
<p><strong>Directions</strong></p>
<p><strong>Train from Schiphol airport</strong></p>
<p>: journey takes about 30 minutes and costs
about 6 Euro,-. Take the train from Schiphol airport to Station Sloterdijk. There you take bus 15 and get off at the Bos en Lommerplein. Walk in the direction the bus is going until the crossing and cross the street to the left. Proceed until the end and turn left. Turn right into the first street, this is the Marieken van Nimwegenstraat. After about 150 meters, on the right hand side, at number 11b <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme Brazil can be found. The entrance is in the garden.
</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Public transport from Amsterdam Central Station</strong>: Bus 21: direction Geuzenveld . Get off at stop Egidiusstraat. Walk from the tram-/ bus stop towards “Domino’s Pizza”. Enter the Egidiusstraat. Turn the second street right into the Marieken van Nimwegenstraat. After about 150 meters, on the left hand side, at number 11b <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme Brazil can be found. The entrance is in the garden.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>By car from direction Den Haag/Utrecht/Amersfoort</strong>: From the A10 take exit S105. At the exit, go straight passing two traffic lights (these are close to each other) to get on the S104 and keep right. At the end of the exit turn right at the traffic lights. Go straight ahead at the 2 traffic lights and at Domino's Pizza turn right into the Egidiusstraat. Turn the second street right into the Marieken van Nimwegenstraat. After about 150 meters, on the left hand side, at number 11b, <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme Brazil can be found. The entrance is in the garden.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>By car from direction Zaandam: take exit S104.
At the end of the exit turn left. Go straight ahead at the 2 traffic lights and at Domino's Pizza turn right into the Egidiusstraat. Turn the second street right into the Marieken van Nimwegenstraat. After about 150 meters, on the left hand side, at number 11b, <strong>10minutes2center</strong> theme Brazil can be found. The entrance is in the garden.</p>
<p>Click <a href="file://localhost/javascript/kaart()">here</a> for a map. </p>
<p><strong>Parking</strong> We recommend parking your car in the guarded and covered parking "P + R" under the Bos en Lommerplein at Leeuwendalersweg 23b. Parking in a "P + R" costs 8 Euro per 24 hours including a return ticket for public transport for up to 5 people, depending on the number of people. Follow the above directions until right after the 2 traffic lights. Turn left at KFC. Follow this road en the curve to the left. At the end of the road you will see the entrance of the parking. Look at www.parkerenamsterdam.nl for more information. Fast, flexible and free with the bike through Amsterdam? Borrow
one or two well-maintained bikes from <strong>10minutes2center</strong>! </p>
<p>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>
<br />
We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!<br />
<br />
Kind regards,</p>
<p>Janeth</p>
<p>+31 630040156</p>
<p>info@10minutes2center.nl</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a pre-payment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The 50% pre-payment is non-refundable at any time, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 21 days before the start of the stay will be charged with 100% of the balance due.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a pre-payment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The 50% pre-payment is non-refundable at any time, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 21 days before the start of the stay will be charged with 100% of the balance due.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="new photo.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_new%20photo.jpg" modified="2024-02-08 03:57:46"><![CDATA[Living area Brazil apartment Amsterdam ]]></image>
      <image name="img_7433.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_7433.jpg" modified="2024-03-12 10:51:57"><![CDATA[Living area Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_7432.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_7432.jpg" modified="2023-10-21 13:53:55"><![CDATA[Living area other angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_7430.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_7430.jpg" modified="2023-10-21 13:53:55"><![CDATA[Living area with television Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_7436.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_7436.jpg" modified="2023-10-21 13:53:58"><![CDATA[Sofa bed Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_7440.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_7440.jpg" modified="2023-10-21 13:53:57"><![CDATA[Sofa bed other angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="09.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_09.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:36:57"><![CDATA[Kitchen with Dining Area Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="10.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_10.jpg" modified="2016-05-08 23:36:58"><![CDATA[Kitchen Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="11.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_11.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:27"><![CDATA[Kitchen Other Angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="12.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_12.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:27"><![CDATA[Dining Area Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="15.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_15.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:27"><![CDATA[Bedroom Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="16.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_16.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:28"><![CDATA[Bedroom Other Angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="13.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_13.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:28"><![CDATA[Bathroom Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="14.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_14.jpg" modified="2014-03-06 13:23:30"><![CDATA[Bathroom Other Angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5852.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5852.jpg" modified="2017-10-15 16:52:16"><![CDATA[Garden Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5857.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5857.jpg" modified="2018-05-09 13:03:29"><![CDATA[Garden other angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5860.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5860.jpg" modified="2018-01-30 11:27:56"><![CDATA[Garden other angle 1 Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5884.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5884.jpg" modified="2018-01-02 11:48:02"><![CDATA[Neighborhood Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5877.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5877.jpg" modified="2018-01-02 11:48:01"><![CDATA[Water View Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5878.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5878.jpg" modified="2018-01-02 11:48:01"><![CDATA[Park Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5881.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5881.jpg" modified="2018-01-02 11:48:01"><![CDATA[Play ground Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="img_5882.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21622_img_5882.jpg" modified="2018-01-19 04:33:35"><![CDATA[Water View other angle Brazil apartment Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2013-12-03 10:29:59</created>
    <modified>2024-05-28 12:27:51</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="21627" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 10" identifier="1569" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21628" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 8" identifier="1567" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21629" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 9" identifier="1568" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21630" name="Fancy Canal View apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0375" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21655" name="Trendy Pijp apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0397" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21658" name="Amstel View apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0398" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21660" name="Prince Royal II houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0401" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21661" name="Prince Royal Suite" identifier="jd" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21678" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 11" identifier="1576" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21679" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 12" identifier="1577" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21680" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 13" identifier="1578" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21711" name="Patrician Suite apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0434" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21712" name="Regent Suite apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0435" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21719" name="Artis Aquarium apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0408" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21720" name="Prince Royal I houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0402" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21721" name="Park Palace apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0404" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21722" name="Park Palace penthouse Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0405" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21723" name="Marigold Suite studio Amsterdam" identifier="#922" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21724" name="City Center apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0410" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21725" name="Marigold II studio Amsterdam" identifier="#922" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21729" name="testproperty B" identifier="456" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21734" name="Tropen Apartment 3" identifier="1902" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21735" name="Tropen Apartment 4" identifier="1903" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21736" name="Tropen Apartment 5" identifier="1904" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21737" name="Tropen Apartment 6" identifier="1905" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21738" name="Tropen Apartment 7" identifier="1906" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21739" name="Tropen Apartment 8" identifier="1907" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21773" name="Modern City studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0403" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21775" name="Lovely City apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0411" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21777" name="Korte Leidse apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0412" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21794" name="Charming Amstel apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0413" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21795" name="De Pijp VIP apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0415" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21819" name="Cosy West apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0417" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21822" name="Wilhelm II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0416" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21823" name="Tulip A apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0421" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21824" name="Tulip B apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0422" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21825" name="Tulip C apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0423" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21826" name="Tulip D apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0427" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21827" name="Tulip E apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0424" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21836" name="Dijk studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0418" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21842" name="Jordaan Marnix Apartment D" identifier="1468" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21844" name="Clerck studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0419" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21846" name="Gerard Dou penthouse Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0425" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21847" name="Gerard Dou apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0426" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21863" name="Rembrandt City apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0420" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21878" name="Staalmeesters III" identifier="1502" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21881" name="Dam Relax apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0430" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21882" name="Wooden apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0429" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21883" name="Eerste Helmers apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0431" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21884" name="Kerkstraat A apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0432" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21885" name="Kerkstraat B apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0433" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21886" name="De Pijp Boutique Apartment 9B" identifier="1570" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21887" name="Govert Flinck apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0428" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21919" name="Vondelgarden Apartment 1" identifier="1641" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21920" name="Vondelgarden Apartment 2" identifier="1642" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21923" name="Brouwers Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#603" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21924" name="Pijp Balcony apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0438" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21926" name="Reguliers Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0437" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21940" name="Spiegel Suite studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0476" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21941" name="Spiegel Family apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0477" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21946" name="Singel apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0440" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21947" name="Singel II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0439" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21948" name="Bloemstraat apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0448" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21949" name="Authentic ship Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0446" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21950" name="Dam Centre apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0507" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21954" name="Test" identifier="#202" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3702,4.89517</gps>
      <address>straat</address>
      <zipcode>1000 AB</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>area</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>3</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>7</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2021-01-01</available_start>
    <available_end>2079-12-31</available_end>
    <floor>0</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>0</size>
    <bedrooms>0</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>0</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>0</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>0</bathrooms>
    <toilets>0</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>none</internet>
    <internet_connection>none</internet_connection>
    <parking>none</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>0</fans>
    <balcony>0</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>none</tv>
    <tv_connection>none</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>0</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>0</oven>
    <microwave>0</microwave>
    <grill>0</grill>
    <hob>0</hob>
    <fridge>0</fridge>
    <freezer>0</freezer>
    <washingmachine>0</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>0</toaster>
    <kettle>0</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>0</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>0</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>0</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>0</coffee>
      <tea>0</tea>
      <milk>0</milk>
      <sugar>0</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>0</linen>
      <towels>0</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>10</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>20</deposit_costs>
    <check_in/>
    <check_out/>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[short description]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="js_01.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/21954_js_01.jpg" modified="2024-09-12 14:47:16"><![CDATA[dit is een foto]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2014-04-14 14:24:29</created>
    <modified>2024-09-12 14:53:28</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="21969" name="Family apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0454" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21971" name="Flower Market apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0444" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21972" name="Centre Rooftop apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0449" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21973" name="Chique Style studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0450" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21974" name="Cosy City Centre studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0445" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21982" name="Charming Family apartment Amsterdam" identifier="#619" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21983" name="Cosy Jordaan apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0456" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="21994" name="Dormir Jordaan II apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0443" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22013" name="Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam" identifier="#622" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3568,4.89784</gps>
      <address>Albert Cuypstraat</address>
      <zipcode>1073 BR </zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>De Pijp Area</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>2</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>3</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2023-04-01</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>3</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>45</size>
    <bedrooms>0</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>0</single_bed>
    <double_bed>1</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>0</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>0</fans>
    <balcony>1</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>flatscreen</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>1</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>0</oven>
    <microwave>0</microwave>
    <grill>0</grill>
    <hob>0</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>0</freezer>
    <washingmachine>1</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>45</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>100</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[Modern studio apartment, housing up to two people in Amsterdam’s Pijp district, overlooking the vibrant Albert Cuyp Market.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Modern studio apartment, housing up to two people in Amsterdam’s Pijp district, overlooking the vibrant Albert Cuyp Market.</strong></p>
<p>The residence boasts an authentic location in a popular neighbourhood brimming with cafes, restaurants, bars and boutiques. Tastefully furnished throughout, the studio benefits from beautiful wooden floors, plenty of natural light and a many modern amenities. The combined living and sleeping area comes equipped with two double beds, large wardrobes, a coffee table, cosy rug, an impressive wall hanging. A flatscreen TV provided for the evening’s entertainment. The kitchen includes a fridge and freezer, offering the option of home dining during your stay. A small yet pleasant balcony allows you to enjoy the sunshine in peace. The bathroom contains a washbasin and a shower, with the toilet situated separately for added convenience. The studio also includes high speed Wi-Fi. Perfect for a family or two couples, the lodging ensures a memorable Amsterdam adventure.</p>
<p>Please note: Our stairs is not child friendly and we do not have a space for prams and strollers. We do not accept families with small children and babies for safety reasons.</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>The accommodation can be found south of the historical centre, lining one of the country’s most famous market streets. Existing over a 100 years, the Albert Cuypmarkt attracts a diverse crowd and enjoys a bustling yet laid back atmosphere, making it the perfect introduction to typical Amsterdam life. This animated attraction is located in the Pijp quarter, renowned for its multicultural population and its multitude of friendly bars, cafes and restaurants, providing more ethnic eateries than any other part of the city.</p>
<p>The studio is superbly placed for discovering Amsterdam’s stunning Canal Belt and its equally picturesque river, the Amstel. Accessible on foot in a matter of minutes, this elegant waterway hosts several cultural venues along its banks, including the Royal Carre Theatre and the Hermitage Museum. The capital’s famous Dam Square can be reached on foot in half an hour or by tram in less than fifteen minutes.</p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,<br />
<br />
Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!<br />
<br />
<b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.<br />
<br />
</b>Please inform us via email: amsterdam-holiday@outlook.com with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible.</p>
<p>
<br />
Once you have arrived at <strong>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring</strong>  please contact us on our check-in telephone <strong>+31 684658367</strong>. This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check-in</strong><br />
Check-in is at the apartment (address: Albert Cuypstraat 262 - III) from 14:00.<br />
<br />
An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be
requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival.For an early or late check-in an additional 30 euro is charged.<u><br />
</u><br />
<strong>Check-out</strong> <br />
Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment. For a late check-out an additional 50 euro is charged.</p>
<p><strong>Payment </strong><br />
The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.<br />
<br />
<strong>Security Deposit</strong></p>
<p>We require a security deposit upon check in. We will hold<strong> Euro 100</strong> in cash upon check-in.
</p>
<p>This amount will be returned to you in cash or by bank transfer after your stay.
</p>
<p>When the check-out is at reasonable times this amount will be returned to you in cash during check-out on the conditions that you have left the apartment in a good condition and no disturbance has occurred. Should you have an early check out the deposit payment will be done by bank transfer.
</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received and the security deposit is settled.</p>
<p><strong>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</strong><br />
<br />
We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!<br />
<br />
Kind regards,</p>
<p>Angel and Denise</p>
<p>+31 684658367</p>
<p>amsterdam-holiday@outlook.com</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="6.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_6.jpg" modified="2023-04-29 03:09:21"><![CDATA[Sitting area Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="room.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_room.jpg" modified="2023-04-29 02:07:24"><![CDATA[Bed Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="dining ta.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_dining%20ta.jpg" modified="2023-05-02 16:58:03"><![CDATA[Dining table Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="bed.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_bed.jpg" modified="2023-05-01 08:41:30"><![CDATA[Bed Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="studio a - i.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_studio%20a%20-%20i.jpg" modified="2023-07-30 11:53:08"><![CDATA[Kitchenette Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="4.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_4.jpg" modified="2023-03-28 13:08:37"><![CDATA[Bathroom sink Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="balcon.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_balcon.jpg" modified="2023-03-28 13:08:35"><![CDATA[Balcony Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0020.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0020.jpg" modified="2017-07-24 11:36:08"><![CDATA[Outdoor View Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0022.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0022.jpg" modified="2018-05-27 08:30:47"><![CDATA[Outdoor View other angle Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0026.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0026.jpg" modified="2017-06-15 07:26:22"><![CDATA[Public Market Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0028.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0028.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 12:42:40"><![CDATA[Public Market other angle Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0032.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0032.jpg" modified="2017-07-24 11:36:08"><![CDATA[Public market Overview Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0029.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0029.jpg" modified="2017-07-24 11:36:08"><![CDATA[Landmark Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0030.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0030.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 12:42:39"><![CDATA[Landmark 1 Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0031.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22013_0031.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 12:42:38"><![CDATA[Street View Albert Cuyp III A studio Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2014-05-02 08:14:01</created>
    <modified>2024-09-13 14:56:44</modified>
  </property>
  <property id="22014" name="WoWow Boutique apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0452" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22015" name="Grand Boutique apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0453" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22020" name="Navy Boutique apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0455" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22032" name="Jordaan studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0457" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22033" name="Leidseplein apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0458" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22039" name="Westerkerk studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0473" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22040" name="Triple A apartment Vinkeveen" identifier="BBA0466" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22041" name="Triple A houseboat Vinkeveen" identifier="BBA0467" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22042" name="Cozy studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0459" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22043" name="Romantic Classic Sail Yacht Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0460" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22044" name="Modern Luxerious houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0461" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22045" name="Keizer studio Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0462" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22052" name="Captains Pride houseboat Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0463" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22053" name="Royal Garden Family House Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0464" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22054" name="Magna Palace apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0465" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22059" name="Luxurious Canal apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0474" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22061" name="Lloyd Design apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0475" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22076" name="Red Carpet apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0487" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22088" name="Stunning View Apartment Vinkeveen" identifier="BBA0478" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22090" name="Rustic Boutique apartment Amsterdam" identifier="BBA0481" status="inactive"/>
  <property id="22097" name="Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam" identifier="#622" status="live" type="apartment">
    <provider id="93" code="AMS" name="Billy Blue Amsterdam"/>
    <location>
      <gps>52.3568,4.89784</gps>
      <address>Albert Cuypstraat</address>
      <zipcode>1073BR</zipcode>
      <city country="NL" gps="52.3731,4.89235">Amsterdam</city>
      <area>De Pijp</area>
    </location>
    <type>leisure,business</type>
    <max_persons>2</max_persons>
    <minimal_nights>3</minimal_nights>
    <maximal_nights>0</maximal_nights>
    <available_start>2014-07-02</available_start>
    <available_end>2025-05-05</available_end>
    <floor>3</floor>
    <stairs>0</stairs>
    <size>45</size>
    <bedrooms>0</bedrooms>
    <single_bed>2</single_bed>
    <double_bed>0</double_bed>
    <single_sofa>0</single_sofa>
    <double_sofa>0</double_sofa>
    <single_bunk>0</single_bunk>
    <bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
    <toilets>1</toilets>
    <elevator>0</elevator>
    <view>street</view>
    <internet>wifi</internet>
    <internet_connection>highspeed</internet_connection>
    <parking>public</parking>
    <airco>0</airco>
    <fans>1</fans>
    <balcony>0</balcony>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <garden>0</garden>
    <roof_terrace>0</roof_terrace>
    <tv>flatscreen</tv>
    <tv_connection>cable</tv_connection>
    <dvd>none</dvd>
    <computer>0</computer>
    <printer>0</printer>
    <iron>0</iron>
    <dishwasher>0</dishwasher>
    <oven>0</oven>
    <microwave>0</microwave>
    <grill>0</grill>
    <hob>0</hob>
    <fridge>1</fridge>
    <freezer>0</freezer>
    <washingmachine>1</washingmachine>
    <dryer>0</dryer>
    <toaster>1</toaster>
    <kettle>1</kettle>
    <coffeemachine>1</coffeemachine>
    <bathtub>0</bathtub>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <shower_regular>1</shower_regular>
    <shower_steam>0</shower_steam>
    <swimmingpool>none</swimmingpool>
    <sauna>none</sauna>
    <hairdryer>1</hairdryer>
    <entresol>0</entresol>
    <wheelchair_friendly>0</wheelchair_friendly>
    <smoking_allowed>0</smoking_allowed>
    <pets_allowed>0</pets_allowed>
    <heating>1</heating>
    <supplies>
      <coffee>1</coffee>
      <tea>1</tea>
      <milk>1</milk>
      <sugar>1</sugar>
      <dishwasher_tablets>0</dishwasher_tablets>
    </supplies>
    <service>
      <linen>1</linen>
      <towels>1</towels>
    </service>
    <cleaning_costs>45</cleaning_costs>
    <deposit_costs>100</deposit_costs>
    <check_in>14:00</check_in>
    <check_out>11:00</check_out>
    <tax>
      <vat>9</vat>
      <other type="relative">12.5</other>
    </tax>
    <prepayment>12.1</prepayment>
    <fee>10</fee>
    <content>
      <short locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[An intimite and cosy studio in Amsterdam, for two people, just a short journey from the centre and the Heineken brewery.]]></short>
      <full locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p><strong>An intimite and cosy studio in Amsterdam, for two people, just a short journey from the centre and the Heineken brewery. </strong></p>
<p>If you are travelling to Amsterdam with your partner and want easy access to the centre and most of the main attractions, then this studio is ideal for you. Located central to Museumplein, the Rijksmuseum, the Heineken brewery and the Keizergracht, you could not wish for a more prime location. The studio itself is warm and welcoming with a beautiful dark-wood floor, elegant lighting, a charming dining table with seating for two guests,, a flat screen TV, a
DVD player and a comfortable single beds. The kitchen area is compact but comes
complete with everything needed to prepare a delicious meal such as microwave. The bathroom has been completely remodelled and
is fitted out with a powerful shower. For your comfort there is a washing
machine, a hairdryer, linen, towels
and a hi-speed Internet connection. For location and quality, this studio will
help make your stay in Amsterdam a memorable one.</p>
<p>Please note: Our stairs is not child friendly and we do not have a space for prams and strollers. We do not accept families with small children and babies for safety reasons.</p>
<p>Registration number: 0363 511D D128 9244 50BB</p>]]></full>
      <area locale="en_gb"><![CDATA[<p>The location of this apartment is premium, with easy access to the Museumplein, with the van Gogh Museum and the Rijksmuseum, with the world famous “Nightwatch” now fully restored to its former glory. A short distance in the other direction is the Hermitage Museum and the Heineken brewery for a great day out when visiting. Of course Amsterdam is world famous for its canals,restaurants and bars on all its numerous Squares. One such square is the Leidesplein and here you can enjoy a cold drink on a terrace, a delicious meal or even visit the legendary Paradiso , where everyone from U2 to the Rolling stones have performed. With so many restaurants around, a strong recommendation is “Greetje” on the Peperstraat near Centraal Station. If museums and bars are not your thing then why not visit the world’s only floating flower market on Singel canal, near Muntplein. Amsterdam is also home to the oldest stock exchange in the world and of course no visit here is complete without seeing the Anne Frank house, in the Jordaan district.</p>]]></area>
      <arrival><![CDATA[<p>Dear guest,<br />
<br />
Thank you for booking your Amsterdam apartment with us!<br />
<br />
<b>Please read the following information carefully as it provides you with the information for a smooth check-in.<br />
<br />
</b>Please inform us via email: amsterdam-holiday@outlook.com with your estimated time of arrival as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Once you have arrived at <strong>Schiphol airport, Amsterdam Central Station or enter Amsterdam’s city ring</strong> please contact us on our check-in telephone<strong> </strong><strong>+31 684658367</strong><em>.</em> This will enable us to estimate your arrival time at the apartment.</p>
<p><strong>Check-in</strong></p>
<p>Check-in is at the apartment (address: Albert Cuypstraat 262,3rd floor) from 14:00.<br />
<br />An early check-in between before 14:00 is not always possible, but can be requested. For availability, please contact us two days prior to your arrival. For an early or late check-in an additional 30 euro is charged.<u><br />
</u><br />
<strong>Check-out</strong> </p>
<p>Check-out is before 11:00 in the morning. A late check-out (till 18:00) can be requested. Please note that this depends on the availability of the apartment. For a late check-out an additional 50 euro is charged.</p>
<p><strong>Payment </strong></p>
<p>The balance due (incl. VAT & Tourist tax) must be paid upon arrival at the apartment. The final payment is done by cash only.<br />
<br />
<strong>Security Deposit</strong></p>
<p>We require a security deposit upon check in. We will hold <strong>Euro 100</strong> in cash upon check-in.
</p>
<p>This amount will be returned to you in cash or by bank transfer after your stay.
</p>
<p>When the check-out is at reasonable times this amount will be returned to you in cash during check-out on the conditions that you have left the apartment in a good condition and no disturbance has occurred. Should you have an early check out the deposit payment will be done by bank transfer.
</p>
<p>Keys will only be handed out, when the final payment is received and the security deposit is settled.</p>
<p><strong>Drugs are strictly prohibited in our apartment.</strong><br />
<br />
We look forward to your arrival and wish you a safe trip!<br />
<br />
Kind regards,</p>
<p>Angel</p>
<p>+31 684658367</p>
<p>amsterdam-holiday@outlook.com</p>]]></arrival>
      <tac><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration-line: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET (Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNoSpacing"> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control, which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife, terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood, adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without notice and refunding payments.</p><p class="MsoNoSpacing"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Cancellation policy</span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Online payment is a prepayment with a balance
due upon arrival</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ul>
	<li><span lang="NL"></span>The prepayment is non-refundable, not even in case of force majeure.</li>
	<li>Bookings cancelled less than 14 days before
arrival will be charged with 100% of the booked amount.</li>
	<li>By accepting the terms and conditions you agree
to charge your credit card with the balance due in case of a late cancellation
or no show situation.</li>
	<li>Cancellations must be made by 12 midday CET
(Central European Time) on the appropriate day </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL">The apartment provider reserves the right to
cancel or alter the booking:<o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"></p>
<ol>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to pay the online
payment and/or remaining balance upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to show their
passport, id card or driver’s license upon arrival.</li>
	<li>If the guest(s) are not able to provide a
security deposit in form of a valid credit card.</li>
	<li>The apartment(s) or part of it is closed due
to circumstances beyond its control.</li>
	<li>It prejudices the reputation or causes or
might cause in the apartment providers opinion, damage to the apartments and
its common areas.</li>
	<li>The apartment provider becomes insolvent or enters
into liquidation or receivership.</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider will not be liable for
any delay, loss, damage or expenses incurred if your booking needs to be
altered or cancelled or the apartment provider is unable to perform the
contractual obligations as a result of events beyond his reasonable control,
which shall include but not be limited to events such as war, civil strife,
terrorist activity, labor disputes, natural or man-made disaster, fire, flood,
adverse weather conditions or change of local government laws.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal">In any of these circumstances the apartment
provider will refund any payments made in advance, but will have no further
liability to the Client. If the apartment provider receives serious complaints
or any disputes arise, he reserves the right to terminate your stay without
notice and refunding payments.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Limitation of liability</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The apartment provider shall not be liable for
any direct or indirect damage that may arise as a consequence of the client's
use of the apartment, including without limitation, damages, insurance, losses
because of fire, robbery or criminal behavior.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><br /></span></strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><b><u>Occupant’s</u></b></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Only persons notified to the apartment
provider upon arrival may occupy the apartment. You may not re-let/sublet the
apartment to any other third party without our prior written approval. The
number of persons permitted to occupy the apartment is limited to the number of
beds available and this limit may not be exceeded without our prior written
approval. The apartment provider reserves the right to refuse admittance to the
apartment if this condition is not complied with. </p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><b><u>Fair Use</u></b><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">You and your party agree to be considerate
tenants and to take good care of the apartment(s) and to leave it in a clean
and tidy condition at the end of your stay. Except in the case of normal wear
and tear you are responsible for any damage to the apartment or its contents during
your stay, which has occurred due to the negligence, willful default or
irresponsible behavior on the part of yourself or those occupying the apartment
or their guests. Any damage must be reported to the apartment provider, without
delay. You and your party also agree not to act in any way that could cause
disturbance to the residents in neighboring properties.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><o:p> </o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><span lang="NL"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Alcohol, Drugs & Tobacco</strong></span><o:p></o:p></span></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">The use of drugs and abuse of alcohol is
strictly prohibited on the premises. The use and possession of hard drugs is
illegal and anyone suspected of either will be reported to the Police. In some
apartments smoking inside is allowed, this is stated on the website. It is not
allowed to smoke marihuana inside the apartments.</p>]]></tac>
    </content>
    <images>
      <image name="photos 00.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2000.jpg" modified="2017-11-27 08:03:40"><![CDATA[Sitting Area Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 01.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2001.jpg" modified="2018-07-06 10:16:19"><![CDATA[Dining Area and kitchen Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 002.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%20002.jpg" modified="2018-07-24 13:19:20"><![CDATA[Coffee machine and kettle Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 02.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2002.jpg" modified="2018-07-24 13:19:21"><![CDATA[Bed Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 03.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2003.jpg" modified="2017-12-26 14:03:18"><![CDATA[Bed other angle Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 004.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%20004.jpg" modified="2018-08-28 09:19:59"><![CDATA[Decorative details Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 04.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2004.jpg" modified="2017-12-26 14:03:22"><![CDATA[Bed with towels Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 05.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2005.jpg" modified="2018-07-24 13:19:42"><![CDATA[Bed with Towels other angle Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="photos 06.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_photos%2006.jpg" modified="2018-07-24 13:19:41"><![CDATA[Beds Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0018.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0018.jpg" modified="2020-01-02 09:06:32"><![CDATA[Bathroom other angle Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0019.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0019.jpg" modified="2018-07-30 12:19:10"><![CDATA[Bathroom Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0022.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0022.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 08:55:55"><![CDATA[Public Market Overview Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0023.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0023.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 08:55:55"><![CDATA[Public Market Overview other angle Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0028.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0028.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 08:55:54"><![CDATA[Public Market Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0029.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0029.jpg" modified="2017-08-14 08:55:54"><![CDATA[Landmark Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="0030.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_0030.jpg" modified="2019-06-13 12:12:35"><![CDATA[Landmark 1 Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="voor_23.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_voor_23.jpg" modified="2019-06-13 12:12:35"><![CDATA[Public market other angle 1 Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="63703.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_63703.jpg" modified="2018-01-26 11:41:25"><![CDATA[Park Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="77811.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_77811.jpg" modified="2018-01-26 11:41:24"><![CDATA[Landmark 2 Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
      <image name="6933311.jpg" url="http://control.bookingmanager.com/data/property/real/22097_6933311.jpg" modified="2018-01-26 11:41:24"><![CDATA[Amsterdam Central Albert Cuyp III B studio Amsterdam]]></image>
    </images>
    <created>2014-06-19 08:07:09</created>
    <modified>2024-08-29 14:23:21</modified>
  </property>
</properties>